// FROM: E:/aspects/cyclomaticComplexityAnalysisStudy/ProductLineHierarchic/src/app/puzzle-builder/puzzle-builder-module-ts
import { NgModule } from "@angular/core";
import { CommonModule } from "@angular/common";
import { PuzzleBuilderRoutingModule } from "./puzzle-builder-routing.module";
import { PuzzleBoardComponent } from "./pages/puzzle-board/puzzle-board.component";
import { PuzzleBuilderComponent } from "./pages/puzzle-builder-component/puzzle-builder.component";
import { MaterialModule } from "../material/material.module";
import { PuzzleChooserComponent } from "./pages/puzzle-chooser/puzzle-chooser.component";
import { RemoveDirective } from "../directives/remove.directive";
import { TemplatePreviewComponent } from "./pages/template-preview/template-preview.component";
import { InsertTemplateImageComponent } from "./pages/insert-template-image/insert-template-image.component";
import { DragAndDropDirective } from "../directives/drag-and-drop.directive";
import { FlexLayoutModule } from "@angular/flex-layout";
import { PuzzleChooserBottomSheetComponent } from "./pages/bottom-sheets/puzzle-chooser-bottom-sheet/puzzle-chooser-bottom-sheet.component";
import { TemplatePreviewBottomSheetComponent } from "./pages/bottom-sheets/template-preview-bottom-sheet/template-preview-bottom-sheet.component";
import { InsertTemplateImageBottomSheetComponent } from "./pages/bottom-sheets/insert-template-image-bottom-sheet/insert-template-image-bottom-sheet.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true" }, "AND": { "OR": { "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" } }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { ZoomManagementComponent } from "./pages/zoom-management/zoom-management.component";
import { FormsModule, ReactiveFormsModule } from "@angular/forms";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "OR": { "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { ZoomMenuComponent } from "./components/zoom-menu/zoom-menu.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "imageGallery": "false", "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { GalleryComponent } from "./pages/gallery/gallery.component";
import { DragAndDropImageComponent } from "./components/drag-and-drop-image/drag-and-drop-image.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "imageGallery": "false", "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { GalleryBottomSheetComponent } from "./pages/bottom-sheets/gallery-bottom-sheet/gallery-bottom-sheet.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true" }, "AND": { "OR": { "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" } }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { ZoomManagementBottomSheetComponent } from "./pages/bottom-sheets/zoom-management-bottom-sheet/zoom-management-bottom-sheet.component";
import { GameConfigurationComponent } from "../game-configuration/game-configuration.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "OR": { "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { ZoomBlockComponent } from "./components/zoom-block/zoom-block.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoomValue": "true", "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { SetZoomComponent } from "./pages/zoom-management/set-zoom/set-zoom.component";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
}
import { SetZoomPositionComponent } from "./pages/zoom-management/set-zoom-position/set-zoom-position.component";
import { DecoratorTypesService } from "../featureManagement/decoratorsVariationPointManagement/decorator-types.service";
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true" }, "AND": { "OR": { "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" } }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declZoomManagementComponent = ZoomManagementComponent;
}
else {
    let declZoomManagementComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "OR": { "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declZoomMenuComponent = ZoomMenuComponent;
}
else {
    let declZoomMenuComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "imageGallery": "false", "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declGalleryComponent = GalleryComponent;
}
else {
    let declGalleryComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "imageGallery": "false", "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declGalleryBottomSheetComponent = GalleryBottomSheetComponent;
}
else {
    let declGalleryBottomSheetComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true" }, "AND": { "OR": { "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" } }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declZoomManagementBottomSheetComponent = ZoomManagementBottomSheetComponent;
}
else {
    let declZoomManagementBottomSheetComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "OR": { "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declZoomBlockComponent = ZoomBlockComponent;
}
else {
    let declZoomBlockComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoomValue": "true", "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declSetZoomComponent = SetZoomComponent;
}
else {
    let declSetZoomComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    const declSetZoomPositionComponent = SetZoomPositionComponent;
}
else {
    let declSetZoomPositionComponent = PuzzleBoardComponent;
}
if ({
    "AND": { "mainPage": "true", "mainNavigation": "true", "AND": { "AND": { "OR": { "AND": { "OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true", "reset": "true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "zoom": "true" }, "returnItem": "true", "showPositionOnBoard": "true", "rotate": "true", "boarderPicture": "true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true", "multiplePuzzleSelect": "true", "randomAngleRotation": "true", "changePuzzleOrdering": "true", "puzzleDrawer": "true", "preview": "true" }, "OR": { "imageLoader": "true", "imageGallery": "true", "puzzleNavigation": "true" }, "puzzleNavigation": "true", "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } }
}) {
    class PuzzleBuilderModule {
    }
}
